Woman Unafraid is a crime, drama film directed by William J. Cowen.
A dedicated and compassionate policewoman risks her job by
offering refuge to a young mother with mob associations.
Crime drama.
Officer Augusta Winthrop, played by Lucile Gleason.
Anthony Desmond, played by Richard 'Skeets' Gallagher.
Peggy, played by Lona Andre.
John, a Sailor, played by Warren Hymer.
Mary Sloan, played by Barbara Weeks.
Kate, played by Ruth Clifford.
The Unafraid is a 1915 American silent drama film directed by Cecil B.
Rita Jolivet completed this film just before boarding
the Lusitania on its final voyage.
The film survives and is preserved in the film archive at George Eastman House.
It was based on a novel by Eleanor M.
The film explores themes of prohibition era, gangster, great depression.
The tone is emotional.